[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This famous exclamation, which has been attributed to ancient scientist Archimedes, is the official state motto of California.", "correct_answer": "Eureka", "incorrect_answers": ["Excelsior!", "Virtute et armis", "Ad astra per aspera"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Women become overweight easier than men.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "An inguinal hernia occurs in the groin, the area between the abdomen and thigh.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the villains nickname in the 1981 movie For  Your Eyes Only?", "correct_answer": "The Dove", "incorrect_answers": ["The Wolf", "The Bear", "The  Owl"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what 1987 horror movie were these lines delivered: I thought Id gone to the limits. I hadnt. The Cenobites gave me an experience beyond limits... pain and pleasure, indivisible.?", "correct_answer": "Hellraiser", "incorrect_answers": ["The Evil Dead", "Nightmare on Elm Street", "The Serpent and the Rainbow"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Alec Newbary was a democrat in the beginning of the film St. Elmos Fire, but later went to work for a Republican senator.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie My Girl, when Vada attends her writing class for the last time, she reads a poem. What is it about?", "correct_answer": "Thomas J.", "incorrect_answers": ["school", "ice cream", "her father"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This actor played Deke Thornton, the man trying to capture The Wild Bunch. He was also the  pessimistic Colonel in The Dirty Dozen.", "correct_answer": "Robert Ryan", "incorrect_answers": ["Ernest Borgnine", "Lee Marvin", "William Holt"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does the Dead Mans Chest contain in the 2006 movie Pirates of the Caribbean: Dead Mans Chest?", "correct_answer": "A heart", "incorrect_answers": ["Pandoras box", "A golden treasure", "A skeleton"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of meat is used for the preparation of Basashi, a popular Japanese dish?", "correct_answer": "Horse meat", "incorrect_answers": ["Goat meat", "Bear meat", "Shark"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The ore and coal rich region of Silesia (pol.: \u015alask, ger.: Schliesien, cz.: Slezsko) was ruled by Germans, Poles, Czechs and Austrians. To which country does it mostly belong today?", "correct_answer": "Poland", "incorrect_answers": ["Slovakia", "Germany", "Czech Republic"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The official currency of Israel is the New Israeli sheqel (NIS).", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]